Paul Baran Papers M1817
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Chron. Files Date:890824 (Container 142, Folder 5)
  Interop 89, "The Path to Open Systems: TCP/IP, OSI and the X Window System"
- Chron. Files Date:900101 (Container 142, Folder 6)
  Addison-Wesley, "Professional Training Resources, 1990"
- Chron. Files Date:900101 (Container 142, Folder 7)
  High Tech Start-Up Algorithms: Programs for Success, Gordon Bell with John McNamara
- Chron. Files Date:900201 (Container 142, Folder 8)
  New Enterprise Associates V, $175,000,000 Limited Partnership Interests
- Chron. Files Date:900312 (Container 142, Folder 9)
  Faxes from Scott Loftesness; Interfax misc.
- Chron. Files Date:900327 (Container 142, Folder 10)
  Interfax misc. (Financial Report, etc)
- Chron. Files Date:900410 (Container 142, Folder 11)
  Slides on "Tutorial on Hardware System Reliability for the Model 10"
- Chron. Files Date:900514 (Container 142, Folder 12)
  Interfax, Marketing Meeting Minutes and Action Items for May 14, 1990; Progress Report, etc.
- Chron. Files Date:900515 (Container 142, Folder 13)
  NEA 1990 Annual Meeting
- Chron. Files Date:900531 (Container 142, Folder 14)
  Wilson, Sonsini, Goodrich & Rosati, First Amended & Restated Registration Rights Agreement
- Chron. Files Date:900604 (Container 142, Folder 15)
  Interfax, Marketing Meeting Minutes for June 4, and June 11, 1990, Financial Report, etc.
- Chron. Files Date:900611 (Container 142, Folder 16)
  Heller, Ehrman, White & McAuliffe, Intellectual Property Counsel; "Connectivity;" Interfax info.
- Chron. Files Date:900127 (Container 142, Folder 17)
  Towards A National Policy for the Information Infrastructure, Paul Baran
- Chron. Files Date:900214 (Container 142, Folder 18)
  A Project to Develop Consensus on Creating the Information Infrastructure of the 21st Century
- Chron. Files Date:900602 (Container 142, Folder 19)
  Gordon Bell's book, Chapters 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10
- Chron. Files Date:900608 (Container 142, Folder 20)
  Digicipher TM HDTV System, General Instrument Corp, Videocipher Division
- Chron. Files Date:900617 (Container 142, Folder 21)
  Fax from Loftesness regarding meeting; Marketing Minutes from June 18, 1990
- Chron. Files Date:900702 (Container 142, Folder 22)
  Marketing Meeting Agenda for July 2, 1990; Loftesness fax re MCI; fax to Vint Cerf re. developing countries
- Chron. Files Date:900705 (Container 142, Folder 23)
  Interfax, monthly financial report, June, 1990
- Chron. Files Date:900717 (Container 142, Folder 24)
  Interfax, Board Meeting, July 17, 1990; monthly progress report; FCC
- Chron. Files Date:900718 (Container 142, Folder 25)
  National Venture Capital Assoc, "Campaign to achieve a meaningful reduction in the capital gains tax"
- Chron. Files Date:900726 (Container 142, Folder 26)
  Review of Gordon Bell draft, "High Tech Startup Algorithms: Problems for Success"
- Chron. Files Date:900727 (Container 142, Folder 27)
  Memo to Interfax investors (interest expressed in next round)
- Chron. Files Date:900731 (Container 142, Folder 28)
  Interfax, Minutes of Meeting of Board of Directors; Amer, Scientist, "The Science of Computing," Dennings
- Chron. Files Date:900803 (Container 142, Folder 29)
  Advent Brochure
- Chron. Files Date:900918 (Container 142, Folder 30)
  The Telco-Cable II Conference, Washington
- Chron Files Date:821201 (Container 143, Folder 1)
  PacketPhone Business Plan
- Chron Files Date:830418 (Container 143, Folder 2)
  PacketPhone Overview
- Chron Files Date:840214 (Container 143, Folder 3)
  Videotex Venture
- Chron Files Date:840626 (Container 143, Folder 4)
  Trintex: a CBS/IBM/Sears Company
- Chron Files Date:840717 (Container 143, Folder 5)
  Hearst Cable Communications
- Chron Files Date:841130 (Container 143, Folder 6)
  PacketDAX
- Chron Files Date:850410 (Container 143, Folder 7)
  Michigan Bell
- Chron Files Date:890801 (Container 143, Folder 8)
  Aug. 1989, chron. files
- Chron Files Date:890901 (Container 143, Folder 9)
  Sept. 1989, chron. files
- Chron Files Date:891001 (Container 143, Folder 10)
  Oct. 1989, chron. files
- Chron Files Date:891101 (Container 143, Folder 11)
  Nov. 1989, chron. files
- Chron Files Date:891201 (Container 143, Folder 12)
  Dec. 1989, chron. files
- Chron Files Date:900101 (Container 143, Folder 13)
  Jan. 1990, chron. files
- Chron Files Date:900201 (Container 143, Folder 14)
  Feb. 1990, chron. files
- Chron Files Date:900301 (Container 143, Folder 15)
  March 1990, chron. files
- Chron Files Date:900531 (Container 143, Folder 16)
  May 1990, chron. files (note: no April)
- Drexel Date:920601 (Container 144, Folder 1)
  Assorted brochures, 1991 and 1992 - Alumni, Annual Reports, etc.
- Drexel Date:920602 (Container 144, Folder 2)
  Book: "Drexel University - A Century of Growth and Challenges"
- Drexel Date:920613 (Container 144, Folder 3)
  Drexel 100 Awards Ceremony
- Drexel Date:920613 (Container 144, Folder 4)
  Assorted press clippings regarding the Centennial
- Drexel Date:920701 (Container 144, Folder 5)
  Alumni Digest of Drexel University, Fall, 1992
- Drexel Date:920922 (Container 144, Folder 6)
  Confirms meeting with Barbara Spiro regarding Drexel
- Drexel Date:921022 (Container 144, Folder 7)
  Maureen Turner's draft for Alumni Digest (request for PB to proof)
- Drexel Date:921221 (Container 144, Folder 8)
  Philadelphia Inquirer story and Drexel's new Strategic Plan
- Drexel Date:930401 (Container 144, Folder 9)
  Drexel: "Partners for the Future," Spring, 1993
- Drexel Date:940413 (Container 144, Folder 10)
  Invitation for Reunion Weekend '94, May 20 - 22
- Drexel Date:930616 (Container 144, Folder 11)
  New York Times: "Drexel U. Hopes to Ride Its Solar-Powered Car Into the Limelight"
- Drexel Date:930730 (Container 144, Folder 12)
  Call for Drexel 100 Nominations
- Drexel Date:930901 (Container 144, Folder 13)
  Final phase of selection of Drexel 100
- Drexel Date:931001 (Container 144, Folder 14)
  Alumni Digest of Drexel University, Winter, 1993
- Drexel Date:931022 (Container 144, Folder 15)
  Information on taking major role in 1994 Reunion activities, May 20 and 21
- Drexel Date:931023 (Container 144, Folder 16)
  Invitation for Anthony J. Drexel Society Dinner
- Drexel Date:931004 (Container 144, Folder 17)
  Information on gathering of Drexel 100, Nov. 5-6, 1993
- Drexel Date:931027 (Container 144, Folder 18)
  President's annual State of the University
- Drexel Date:931215 (Container 144, Folder 19)
  Year-end request for support
- Drexel Date:940617 (Container 144, Folder 20)
  Thank you letter for $2,500 for Unrestricted Annual Fund
- Drexel Date:940701 (Container 144, Folder 21)
  Drexel: "Partners for the Future," Fall, 1994
- Drexel Date:941001 (Container 144, Folder 22)
  Alumni Digest of Drexel University, Winter/Spring 1994
- Drexel Date:951207 (Container 144, Folder 23)
  Invitation for a luncheon honoring members of The Drexel 100, May 4
- Drexel Date:960313 (Container 144, Folder 24)
  Invitation for 1996 Induction Ceremony for The Drexel 100, May 4
- Drexel Date:960401 (Container 144, Folder 25)
  Drexel Vanguard, Spring 1996
- Drexel Date:960701 (Container 144, Folder 26)
  Alumni Magazine of Drexel University, Fall 1996
- Drexel Date:961007 (Container 144, Folder 27)
  Sigma Alpha Mu - need money for Repair Fund for the House
- Drexel Date:961121 (Container 144, Folder 28)
  Congratulations on selection for (NEA)National Academy of Engineering, (Papadakis & Wulf)
- Drexel Date:970207 (Container 144, Folder 29)
  Fax to Vernon Waring regarding speech given to C & C Fdn, Tokyo, with Cerf
- Drexel Date:971001 (Container 144, Folder 30)
  Packet of information on Drexel
- Drexel Date:970614 (Container 144, Folder 31)
  PB's speech at Commencement, June 14, 1997
- Drexel Date:970729 (Container 144, Folder 32)
  URLs for old papers
- Drexel Date:970626 (Container 144, Folder 33)
  Thank you letter to Woehrle for courtesy during Commencement weekend, Drexel materials
- Drexel Date:971016 (Container 144, Folder 34)
  Invitation to join Jiang Zemin, President of People's Republic of China, Oct. 30, 1997
- Drexel Date:970417 (Container 144, Folder 35)
  Details on PB's visit to Drexel, April 19 (Pyramid Club)
- Drexel Date:970803 (Container 144, Folder 36)
  Alumni Endorsement Grant program, other materials
- Drexel Date:980612 (Container 144, Folder 37)
  Invitation recognizing The Drexel 100, June 12, 1998, Gladwyne
- Drexel Date:980223 (Container 144, Folder 38)
  Invitation to induction ceremony for The Drexel 100
- Drexel Date:980109 (Container 144, Folder 39)
  General information in preparation for Reunion Weekend
- Marconi Date:090226 (Container 145, Folder 1)
  PB's letter for 17th Marconi Award written by Gerald Estrin
- Marconi Date:901120 (Container 145, Folder 2)
  Estrin's letter to Cerf with notification PB selected for Award
- Marconi Date:910416 (Container 145, Folder 3)
  List to be invited to PB's Award
- Marconi Date:910326 (Container 145, Folder 4)
  List of Marconi Fellows commissioned works and bio material
- Marconi Date:910621 (Container 145, Folder 5)
  Citation - PB for Marconi Award
- Marconi Date:910423 (Container 145, Folder 6)
  Schedule for Ceremonies in Nova Scotia
- Marconi Date:910617 (Container 145, Folder 7)
  Letter of Welcome to Halifax from Cultural Services Officer
- Marconi Date:910618 (Container 145, Folder 8)
  Schedule for Ceremony and Ancillary Events
- Marconi Date:910620 (Container 145, Folder 9)
  PB's Award acceptance speech
- Marconi Date:910620 (Container 145, Folder 10)
  Schedule of events for Dinner Program Award Ceremony, plus handouts
- Marconi Date:910621 (Container 145, Folder 11)
  Chronicle-Herald "Governor General Presents Awards" (mentions PB)
- Marconi Date:910622 (Container 145, Folder 12)
  Chronicle-Herald "Packet Switching Inventor Aims to Make Planet Better Place (about PB)
- Marconi Date:911113 (Container 145, Folder 13)
  PB's thank-you to Gioia for sending video tape of awards (and other letters)
- Marconi Date:950519 (Container 145, Folder 14)
  Final schedule of events for Italy
- Marconi Date:950623 (Container 145, Folder 15)
  PB's speech, "Is the UHF Frequency Shortage a Self Made Problem?"
- Marconi Date:960604 (Container 145, Folder 16)
  Evelyn's folder of the London events
- Marconi Date:961030 (Container 145, Folder 17)
  Seminar with the Italian Academy on "Heritage of Marconi's Invention & the Future of Telecommunication"
- Marconi Date:970421 (Container 145, Folder 18)
  Meyerson's letter regarding signing of agreement between Columbia and Marconi (4/22/97)
- Marconi Date:990101 (Container 145, Folder 19)
  CED, January 1999, article on Yassini, "Fulfills A Tall Order"
- Marconi Date:991205 (Container 145, Folder 20)
  Performance of splitterless DSL at higher speeds (mentions Cioffi)
- Marconi Date:020411 (Container 145, Folder 21)
  Patent Application, Smith et al, (search results - ambiguous search query)
- Marconi Date:021107 (Container 145, Folder 22)
  Board meeting, Nov. 7, at Columbia
- Marconi Date:021120 (Container 145, Folder 23)
  Estimate of Budget, submitted Nov. 20
- Marconi Date:030123 (Container 145, Folder 24)
  Marconi Scholarly Research & Book Proposal: 10 year plan
- Marconi Date:030123 (Container 145, Folder 25)
  Information from Darcy regarding Board Meeting in May
- Marconi Date:031027 (Container 145, Folder 26)
  PB's memo regarding the selection process ("Comparing Eggs to Chickens"
- Marconi Date:030224 (Container 145, Folder 27)
  Darcy's letter regarding Marconi nomination for Award
- Marconi Date:030307 (Container 145, Folder 28)
  Francesco's letter regarding highlights of Tim Berners-Lee's Award, and appeal for donations
- Marconi Date:030401 (Container 145, Folder 29)
  Spreading the Word - CD mailed to media outlets prior to Marconi Anniversary Celebration
- Marconi Date:030523 (Container 145, Folder 30)
  Items included in Board meeting packets
- Marconi Date:030812 (Container 145, Folder 31)
  Information regarding mock up of hypothetical biography
- Marconi Date:030926 (Container 145, Folder 32)
  Thank you letter from Jay to Bill for $5,000 donation
- Marconi Date:030930 (Container 145, Folder 33)
  Morgan Stanley Statement Sept. 30, 2003
- Marconi Date:031002 (Container 145, Folder 34)
  Board meeting, Oct. 2, at Columbia. Report from Gronner on Public Relations activities
- Marconi Date:031016 (Container 145, Folder 35)
  Report of SAC Meeting, held Oct. 2
- Marconi Date:031025 (Container 145, Folder 36)
  Internet Pioneers by Marc Andreesen
- Marconi Date:031026 (Container 145, Folder 37)
  Martin Cooper: Cell Phone 'Father' Squeezes Spectrum 145 38 031031 Marconi Jay's 'thank you' to PB for help with 2003 Award Dinner (Gallager & Metcalfe), CV, articles 145 39 031107 Marconi Ash's comments on Structuring the Selection Process"
- Marconi Date:031127 (Container 145, Folder 40)
  Information on Google (founders and the company)
- Marconi Date:031208 (Container 145, Folder 41)
  Announcement that Robert Kahn was selected for the 20th Marconi Award
- Marconi Date:031231 (Container 145, Folder 42)
  Morgan Stanley Statement Dec. 31, 2003
- Marconi Date:040506 (Container 145, Folder 43)
  Board Meeting, Mudd Hall, May 14
- Marconi Date:040112 (Container 145, Folder 44)
  Marconi Fellowship, 30th Anniversary Book
- Marconi Date:051103 (Container 145, Folder 45)
  Board Meeting, Fu School of Engineering, Nov. 3
- NAE Date:960214 (Container 146, Folder 1)
  (National Academy of Engineering) PB Election to NAE
- NAE Date:961018 (Container 146, Folder 2)
  Wm. Wulf, Pres, update on organization
- NAE Date:961101 (Container 146, Folder 3)
  Information on Charles Stark Draper prize
- NAE Date:961106 (Container 146, Folder 4)
  Section 5 discussion and summarization from Oct. 2, 1996
- NAE Date:961120 (Container 146, Folder 5)
  Monthly update from Wulf
- NAE Date:961220 (Container 146, Folder 6)
  Minutes of Business Session held on Oct. 2, 1996
- NAE Date:970301 (Container 146, Folder 7)
  Ballot for 1997 NAE Officer and Councillor election
- NAE Date:970107 (Container 146, Folder 8)
  Call for nominations for 1997 Founders Award & for the Arthur M. Bueche award
- NAE Date:970214 (Container 146, Folder 9)
  Academy elects 85 members and 8 foreign associates
- NAE Date:970415 (Container 146, Folder 10)
  Announcement of Wm. Wulf as President
- NAE Date:970520 (Container 146, Folder 11)
  1997 Data Verification Form
- NAE Date:970201 (Container 146, Folder 12)
  Members Comments
- NAE Date:970214 (Container 146, Folder 13)
  1977 NAE National Meeting
- NAE Date:970721 (Container 146, Folder 14)
  Search for candidates, change of annual meeting, request for "Use of Tech. to Strengthen K-12 Educ."
- NAE Date:970904 (Container 146, Folder 15)
  Planet Neighborhood WETA/NEA Program
- NAE Date:970924 (Container 146, Folder 16)
  Survey of Members
- NAE Date:970929 (Container 146, Folder 17)
  Section 5 Meeting, Oct. 6, 1988
- NAE Date:971007 (Container 146, Folder 18)
  Agenda for Oct. 7, 2009
- NAE Date:971121 (Container 146, Folder 19)
  Wulf's letter to members regarding FACA; observations on NAE Independent Programs
- NAE Date:980224 (Container 146, Folder 20)
  Section 5, Computer Science Ballot, Officers & Committees
- NAE Date:980105 (Container 146, Folder 21)
  Request for nominations for 1998 Founders Award
- NAE Date:980121 (Container 146, Folder 22)
  Wulf's update on activities
- NAE Date:980225 (Container 146, Folder 23)
  PB congratulates Uncapher on election to NAE
- NAE Date:980227 (Container 146, Folder 24)
  Wulf's request to involve members in strategic planning and update
- NAE Date:980415 (Container 146, Folder 25)
  Election results for Officers and Councillors
- NAE Date:980520 (Container 146, Folder 26)
  Draft of Strategic Plan Structure and dinner hosted by Gordon Moore
- NAE Date:980608 (Container 146, Folder 27)
  Wulf's restructuring of National Research Council (NRC) and international activities
- NAE Date:980813 (Container 146, Folder 28)
  Request for suggestions for Nominating Committee
- NAE Date:980916 (Container 146, Folder 29)
  Agenda for business session, Oct. 5, and Report of the President
- NAE Date:981005 (Container 146, Folder 30)
  Minutes of NAE Computer Science & Engineering Section, Oct. 5
- NAE Date:981110 (Container 146, Folder 31)
  Wulf's update to members and comments on Annual Meeting
- NAE Date:981113 (Container 146, Folder 32)
- NAE Date:990104 (Container 146, Folder 33)
  Request for nominations for 1999 Founders Award
- NAE Date:990104 (Container 146, Folder 34)
  Final Ballot booklet
- NAE Date:990108 (Container 146, Folder 35)
  Survey on Elections of Officers & Councillors
- NAE Date:990212 (Container 146, Folder 36)
  Registration for National Meeting, Feb. 12, 1999, Irvine
- NAE Date:990303 (Container 146, Folder 37)
  March 19 regional meeting; request for registration
- NAE Date:990322 (Container 146, Folder 38)
  Section 5, request for nominations for Section Leadership & Nominating Committee
- NAE Date:990430 (Container 146, Folder 39)
  Date Verification Form
- NAE Date:990507 (Container 146, Folder 40)
  Results of elections; Lance Davis new Executive Director; Kumho case
- NAE Date:990729 (Container 146, Folder 41)
  Evaluation of candidates; member comments
- NAE Date:990915 (Container 146, Folder 42)
  Membership access to web NAE site
- NAE Date:991002 (Container 146, Folder 43)
  1999 Annual Meeting (Oct. 5): "Urbanization: The Engineering Challenges"
- NAE Date:991025 (Container 146, Folder 44)
  Wulf on "Technological Literacy"
- NAE Date:991003 (Container 146, Folder 45)
  PB registration and brochure for NAE 1999 Annual Meeting
- NAE Date:000201 (Container 146, Folder 46)
  Wulf's review of the prior year
- NAE Date:000331 (Container 146, Folder 47)
  Biographies of Committee Members
- NAE Date:000501 (Container 146, Folder 48)
  List of Nominating Committee and invitation to suggest new candidates
- NAE Date:000509 (Container 146, Folder 49)
  Data Verification Form
- NAE Date:000717 (Container 146, Folder 50)
- NAE Date:001001 (Container 146, Folder 51)
  Statement of Purpose
- B. Franklin Date:990001 (Container 147, Folder 1)
  Annual Report, 1999
- B. Franklin Date:991218 (Container 147, Folder 2)
  Science News Online: "Imagine That: Animal Magnetism Exposed" (& Other Articles)
- B. Franklin Date:000116 (Container 147, Folder 3)
  PB Hand-written Notes Outlining the Half-hour Movie
- B. Franklin Date:000427 (Container 147, Folder 4)
  Awards Program Booklet
- B. Franklin Date:000510 (Container 147, Folder 5)
  Mention of 8 x 10 Photo from Del Reddy
- B. Franklin Date:000808 (Container 147, Folder 6)
  Nomination of IEEE Internet Award - letter from Fenner to Uncapher
- B. Franklin Date:000817 (Container 147, Folder 7)
  Ltr. To Fenner Regarding Nomination Package for PB
- B. Franklin Date:001016 (Container 147, Folder 8)
  Recommended for Award by International Science Selection Committee
- B. Franklin Date:001017 (Container 147, Folder 9)
  Awards Program - Need Information on PB
- B. Franklin Date:001117 (Container 147, Folder 10)
  Request for Information for PB's Public Relations Packet
- B. Franklin Date:001018 (Container 147, Folder 11)
  Information to PB Regarding the Arrangements for Award Program
- B. Franklin Date:001206 (Container 147, Folder 12)
  Science Award Program Honors World's Top Scientists (PB Wins $250,000 for Internet Work)
- B. Franklin Date:001212 (Container 147, Folder 13)
  The Technical History of the Internet (includes PB Annotated Slides)
- B. Franklin Date:001213 (Container 147, Folder 14)
  Awards Program Information - PB as Corporate Chair
- B. Franklin Date:001213 (Container 147, Folder 15)
  On the Future of Telecommunications given at Franklin Inst. Committee on Arts & Science
- B. Franklin Date:001213 (Container 147, Folder 16)
- B. Franklin Date:001213 (Container 147, Folder 17)
  Schedule for Committee on Science and the Arts
- B. Franklin Date:001214 (Container 147, Folder 18)
  PB Slides for his Talk
- B. Franklin Date:001215 (Container 147, Folder 19)
  Ken Kirby - Corporate Support for 2001 Awards Program
- B. Franklin Date:001215 (Container 147, Folder 20)
- B. Franklin Date:010108 (Container 147, Folder 21)
  Jamie's notes on PB's Comments from Interview She Taped
- B. Franklin Date:010123 (Container 147, Folder 24)
  FI News Release, "Bower Award Laureates Announced, BP Wins $250,000
- B. Franklin Date:010124 (Container 147, Folder 22)
  Philadelphia Inquirer, "Scientist Will be Honored for Keeping Web Untangles" (PB)
- B. Franklin Date:010319 (Container 147, Folder 23)
  SIGCOMM '99 Tutorial Session Notes (Boston), sent to McWilliams
- B. Franklin Date:010321 (Container 147, Folder 26)
  PB's Guest List for 4/26 Ceremony
- B. Franklin Date:010402 (Container 147, Folder 27)
  Tax Advice from Morgan, Lewis & Bockius on PB's Award
- B. Franklin Date:010402 (Container 147, Folder 28)
  Kirby's Letter Acknowledging PB's Check for $250,000 (Bower Prize)
- B. Franklin Date:010402 (Container 147, Folder 29)
  Full Packet of Information on Upcoming Awards Week Events
- B. Franklin Date:010417 (Container 147, Folder 31)
  PB Private Luncheon - Invitation & Guest List
- B. Franklin Date:010424 (Container 147, Folder 32)
  Awards Convocation Booklet, April 24 - 26
- B. Franklin Date:010424 (Container 147, Folder 33)
  2001 Awards Week's Schedule
- B. Franklin Date:010426 (Container 147, Folder 34)
  Photos for Press (Includes PBP
- B. Franklin Date:010426 (Container 147, Folder 35)
  Awards Dinner Program, Cokie Roberts, MC
- B. Franklin Date:010426 (Container 147, Folder 36)
  FI (Hall of the Institute) Investigating the Work of PB
- B. Franklin Date:010426 (Container 147, Folder 37)
  Copies of the Bower Awards Laureates (Including PB)
- B. Franklin Date:010501 (Container 147, Folder 38)
  Ltr. From Lado Thanking PB for Assistance during Awards Week
- B. Franklin Date:010503 (Container 147, Folder 38)
  Ltr. From Wint thanking PB for Joining FI for the 2001 Awards Week
- B. Franklin Date:010511 (Container 147, Folder 40)
  Invitation to "Sail to KidScience: The Island of the Elements"
- B. Franklin Date:010520 (Container 147, Folder 41)
  2001 Bower Award & Prize for Achievement in Science (PB)
- B. Franklin Date:010520 (Container 147, Folder 42)
  PB's Evaluation of the Award Events
- B. Franklin Date:010605 (Container 147, Folder 43)
  Info. on the FI Video Awards Ceremony
- B. Franklin Date:010605 (Container 147, Folder 44)
  Philadelphia News - Write Up on BP Winning 2001 Award and Donating Prize back to FI
- B. Franklin Date:011203 (Container 147, Folder 45)
  Invitation from Hamilton & Kermes to Attend the 2002 Awards Ceremony
- B. Franklin Date:020425 (Container 147, Folder 46)
  Awards Program, Ed Bradley, MC
- C & C Fdn. Date:661030 (Container 148, Folder 1)
  C & C Citation for 1996 C & C Prize (PB)
- C & C Fdn. Date:951201 (Container 148, Folder 2)
  1995 C & C Prize Ceremony Booklet, and list of recipients
- C & C Fdn. Date:961201 (Container 148, Folder 3)
  1966 C & C Prize Ceremony Booklet, and list of recipients
- C & C Fdn. Date:960726 (Container 148, Folder 4)
  Notification that PB won 1996 C & C Prize, along with Cerf and Berners-Lee
- C & C Fdn. Date:961016 (Container 148, Folder 5)
  Revised invitation to Japanese Cabke Industries
- C & C Fdn. Date:961026 (Container 148, Folder 6)
  Itinerary - Far East
- C & C Fdn. Date:961030 (Container 148, Folder 7)
  Commemorative Speech at C & C Prize Ceremony (by Ronald Rohrer
- C & C Fdn. Date:961031 (Container 148, Folder 8)
  Presentation: NEC's Business Domain & Worldwide Electronics Supplier's Ranking
- C & C Fdn. Date:971201 (Container 148, Folder 9)
  NEC: Guide to NEC Abiko
- C & C Fdn. Date:011201 (Container 148, Folder 10)
  2001 List of Recipients of C & C Prize
- C & C Fdn. Date:020401 (Container 148, Folder 11)